Dr. Stephen Corwin Cameron Park Zoo records, Inclusive: 1965-2015, undated, Bulk: 1982-1995
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Research Materials, 1976-1998, undated; 5
  - Waco Visitor Information, 1983-1988, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Writing Instructions, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Zoo Related Publications, 1976, 1992-1995, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Zoological Societies, 1977-1991 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Waco Zoological Societies, 1976-2012, undated; 6
  This series includes documents related to the Cameron Park Zoological Society and its predecessor, the Central Texas Zoological and Botanical Society. These documents include administrative materials, such as professional correspondence, committee lists and meeting minutes, and member lists. The series also includes recruitment information for the societies.
  - Cameron Park Zoological Society Board, 1992-2012, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Cameron Park Zoological Society Bylaws, 1990-1997 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Cameron Park Zoological Society Committees, 1991-1994, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Cameron Park Zoological Society Correspondence, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Cameron Park Zoological Society Endowment, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Cameron Park Zoological Society Lists of Names, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Cameron Park Zoological Society Meetings, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Cameron Park Zoological Society Memorandums, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Cameron Park Zoological Society Newsletter, undated (Box [1029] OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Cameron Park Zoological Society Publications, 1991-1997 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Cameron Park Zoological Society Zootrackers, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Central Texas Zoological Society, 1982-1988, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Central Texas Zoological Society Bylaws, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Central Texas Zoological Society Committees, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Central Texas Zoological Society Correspondence, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Central Texas Zoological Society Events, 1976, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Central Texas Zoological Society Friends of the Zoo, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Central Texas Zoological Society Membership, 1978, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Central Texas Zoological Society Newspapers, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Central Texas Zoological Society Region 9 Arabian Championship Horse Show, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Central Texas Zoological Society Region 9 Arabian Championship Horse Show Photographs, circa 1978 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Central Texas Zoological Society Restatement of Cash, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Dr. Stephen Corwin, 1969-2015, undated; 7
  This series contains documents related to the personal life of Dr. Stephen Corwin, including personal correspondence, materials related to his professional practice, brochures for Wake Forest University, and materials related to his son, Tim Corwin.
  - Birthday Card, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Collected Materials, 1979-1987, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1992, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - McLennan Community College, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Property Documentation, 1969, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Rotary Club, 1977-2015 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Rusty Corbin, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Scholarly Journals, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Tax Laws, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Timothy Corwin, 1980-1993 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Travel Brochures, undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Wake Forest University, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - American Zoos, circa 1970-1978 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Media, circa 1970-1989, undated; 8
  This series contains photographs and negatives related to the campaign for a zoo in Cameron Park and the early days of the Cameron Park Zoo, photographs of the Central Texas Zoo, and landscape negatives and slides featuring scenes from zoos across the United States.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  35 mm slide; Photo negative; Photographic print
  - American Zoos, circa 1970-1978 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Band Campaign, circa 1989 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Cameron Park Zoo, circa 1993 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Cameron Park Zoo Negatives, circa 1989 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Central Texas Zoo, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Events, undated (Box [1029] OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Event Photographs, circa 1983 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Landscapes, undated (Box 15, Folder 30)